jabcomix.com 2013-09-25

# JABcomix :: Privacy Policy

JABcomix.com respects each individual’s right to personal privacy. We will only collect and use information through our Web site in the ways disclosed in this statement.

**  
Membership/Paid Subscription**  
All credit card, checks, and phone billing subscriptions are processed safely by a third party billing processor, Verotel. With this being the case, we do not store nor have access to your sensitive credit card, debit card, or checking account information. Verotel has its own [privacy statement](https://secure.verotel.com/privacy_statement.html) regarding how it processes transactions. 

W

e log your username and ip address to ensure that passes are not abused, shared, or compromised. We also utilize cookies for authentication. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. The cookie issued by our site is used to authenticate you as a valid member and can also be used to save your username and password on our login page.

**News/Forum**  
Please be advised that information posted in our news/forum becomes public knowledge as the forum and all its contents is freely accessible. Registered users to our news/forum have the option to hide their email from the public in their news/forum profiles. Your ip address is logged with each post you make to prevent abusive behavior. Cookies are also utilized to save your news/forum username and password and forum login session.

As a registered user of our forum, your email address may also be added to our newsletter (see below).

**Newlsetter**  
Registered users of our newsletter will receive periodic emails from us regarding special announcements, new comic issues or developments, images, stories, and other JAB related content. Please be aware that by registering to our newsletter you agree to receive these emails which will contain adult content. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we make available the option to opt-out of our newsletter.

**Email and Contact Information**  
We will not share your email address or other contact related information with any third parties outside of our parent company XPosh LLC. Any email solicitations or newsletters sent by XPosh sites will include the option of opting out of their respective mailing lists. We will not contact you by phone or postal mail, nor will we share any of this information with other parties.

**  
Chat and Member Polls**  
We may occassionally monitor our chat rooms for abusive practices. Your ip address is logged in our chat to prevent abuse. Your ip address and cookies are utilized to prevent cheating and abuse in our Member Polls.

**  
Exceptions**  
If you distribute our copyrighted content without our permission you waive ALL rights listed in this privacy policy.

**  
Other Disclosures  
**In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you: 

(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk)

**Policy Amendments**  
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. 

**Contact**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, you may contact us by [email](mailto:webmaster@jabcomix.com).
